Guide to the Washington State Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION, 1908-1980; RECORD GROUP I
  - ECONOMIC SECURITY PROGRAM RECORDS, SERIES VIII
    - NEGOTIATION AND AGREEMENT RECORDS, 1943-1975; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 4/29-6/20, 23/42, 32/14-32/31, 44/28-46/49, 57/12-57/17, 67/19-67/22)
      - Our Lady of Lourdes Hospital, Pasco (part 2 of 2), 1955-1960 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Our Lady of Lourdes Hospital, Pasco (part 1 of 3), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Our Lady of Lourdes Hospital, Pasco (part 2 of 3), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Our Lady of Lourdes Hospital, Pasco (part 3 of 3), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Pierce County Hospital Council (part 1 of 2), 1958-1963 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Pierce County Hospital Council (part 2 of 2), 1958-1963 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Providence Hospital, Seattle, 1948-1961 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Pullman Memorial Hospital (part 1 of 2), 1952-1967 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Pullman Memorial Hospital (part 2 of 2), 1952-1967 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Renton Hospital, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Sacred Heart Hospital, Spokane, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Sacred Heart Hospital, Spokane, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Sacred Heart Hospital, Spokane (part 1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - Sacred Heart Hospital, Spokane (part 2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 5/27)
      - Seattle-King County Department of Public Health (part 1 of 3), 1948-1965 (Box-folder 5/28)
      - Seattle-King County Department of Public Health (part 2 of 3), 1948-1965 (Box-folder 5/29)
      - Seattle-King County Department of Public Health (part 3 of 3), 1948-1965 (Box-folder 5/30)
      - Seattle-King County Department of Public Health, 1966 (Box-folder 5/31)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 5/32)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council (part 1 of 2), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council (part 2 of 2), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council (part 1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council (part 2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council (part 1 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council (part 2 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Seattle General Hospital, 1948-1961 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Skagit Valley Hospital, Mount Vernon, 1953-1965 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council (part 1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council (part 2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - City of Spokane Health Department (part 1 of 2), 1959-1965 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - City of Spokane Health Department (part 2 of 2), 1959-1965 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - Swedish Hospital, Seattle, 1949-1961 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - Virginia Mason Hospital, Seattle, 1948-1961 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - Washington State Department of Institutions, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - Western State Hospital (part 1 of 2), 1949-1966 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - Western State Hospital (part 2 of 2), 1949-1966 (Box-folder 6/18)
      - Yakima County Health District, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - Yakima County Health District, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - School nurses, 1957-1967 (Box-folder 32/14)
      - Bellingham school nurses, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 32/15)
      - Everett Community College nursing faculty, 1968 (Box-folder 32/16)
      - Kennewick Public Schools, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 32/17)
      - Longview school nurses, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 32/18)
      - Moses Lake school nurses, 1956-1962 (Box-folder 32/19)
      - Omak Public School District, 1969 (Box-folder 32/20)
      - Snohomish Health District (part 1 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 32/21)
      - Snohomish Health District (part 2 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 32/22)
      - Snohomish Health District (part 3 of 3), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 32/23)
      - Snohomish County public health nurses resignation letters, 1967 (Box-folder 32/24)
      - Tacoma General School of Nursing, 1964 (Box-folder 32/25)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department (part 1 of 2), 1962-1967 (Box-folder 32/26)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department (part 2 of 2), 1962-1967 (Box-folder 32/27)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department supervisors, 1964 (Box-folder 32/28)
      - Tacoma school nurses, 1953 (Box-folder 32/29)
      - Washington State Department of Institutions (part 1 of 2), 1960-1967 (Box-folder 32/30)
      - Washington State Department of Institutions (part 2 of 2), 1960-1967 (Box-folder 32/31)
      - Bellingham and Whatcom County Department of Public Health, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 44/28)
      - Bellingham Visiting Nurse Association, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 44/29)
      - Benton-Franklin County Health Department, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 44/30)
      - Bethlehem Steel, 1967 (Box-folder 44/31)
      - Boeing Company, 1956-1960 (Box-folder 44/32)
      - Boeing Company, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 44/33)
      - Boeing Company (part 1 of 2), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 44/34)
      - Boeing Company (part 2 of 2), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 44/35)
      - Boeing Health and Welfare Plan, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 44/36)
      - Bon Marche Department Store, 1967 (Box-folder 45/1)
      - Bremerton-Kitsap County Health Department, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 45/2)
      - Cascade Valley Hospital, Arlington, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 45/3)
      - Chelan-Douglas County Health Department, Wenatchee, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 45/4)
      - Clark-Skamania Health District, 1952-1969 (Box-folder 45/5)
      - Continental Can Company, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 45/6)
      - Cowlitz-Wahkiakum Public Health Department, Longview, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 45/7)
      - Deaconess Hospital, Spokane, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 45/8)
      - Doctors Hospital, Seattle, 1948-1959 (Box-folder 45/9)
      - Edgecliff Sanatorium, Spokane, 1950-1966 (Box-folder 45/10)
      - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers Section diploma school instructors questionnaire, 1965 (Box-folder 45/11)
      - General duty employment standards, 1943-1957 (Box-folder 45/12)
      - Good Samaritan Hospital, Puyallup, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 45/13)
      - Good Samaritan Nursing Home, Spokane Valley, 1966 (Box-folder 45/14)
      - Grays Harbor Community Hospital, Aberdeen, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 45/15)
      - Grays Harbor-Pacific Health District, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 45/16)
      - Group Health Cooperative, 1969 (Box-folder 45/17)
      - Holy Family Hospital, Spokane, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 45/18)
      - Interlake Manor Nursing Home, Bellevue, 1965 (Box-folder 45/19)
      - Island County Health Department, 1964 (Box-folder 45/20)
      - Island Hospital, Anacortes, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 45/21)
      - Kennewick General Hospital, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 45/22)
      - King County Hospital supervisors, Seattle, 1959-1966 (Box-folder 45/23)
      - Kittitas County Health Department, 1954-1963 (Box-folder 45/24)
      - Kittitas Valley Community Hospital, Ellensburg (part 1 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box-folder 45/25)
      - Kittitas Valley Community Hospital, Ellensburg (part 2 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box-folder 45/26)
      - Klickitat Valley Hospital, Goldendale, 1952-1968 (Box-folder 45/27)
      - Maynard Hospital, Seattle, 1948-1964 (Box-folder 45/28)
      - Mid-Valley Hospital, Omak, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 45/29)
      - Mount Linton Hospital, Metaline Falls, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 45/30)
      - Mountain View General Hospital, Tacoma, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 45/31)
      - Newport Community Hospital, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 45/32)
      - Northern Pacific Beneficial Association, Tacoma, 1952-1961 (Box-folder 45/33)
      - Northern Pacific Beneficial Association, Tacoma, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 45/34)
      - Northern Pacific Railway stewardess-nurses, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 45/35)
      - Ocean Beach Hospital, Ilwaco, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 45/36)
      - Olympic Memorial Hospital supervisors, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 45/37)
      - Overlake Memorial Hospital, Bellevue, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 45/38)
      - Pacific Car and Foundry Co., 1954 (Box-folder 45/39)
      - Pend Oreille County Health Department, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 45/40)
      - Pierce County Hospital Council, 1965 (Box-folder 45/41)
      - Pierce County Hospital Council negotiations, 1969 (Box-folder 45/42)
      - Port Townsend Medical Building, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 45/43)
      - Private Duty Section fees, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 45/44)
      - Private Duty Section fees questionnaire, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 45/45)
      - Providence Hospital, Everett, 1952-1963 (Box-folder 45/46)
      - Riverton Heights Convalescent Home, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 45/47)
      - Samaritan Hospital, Moses Lake, 1953-1968 (Box-folder 45/48)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council Merit Plan Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 45/49)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council Negotiating Committee roll call, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 45/50)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council nurse rosters (part 1 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 45/51)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council nurse rosters (part 2 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 45/52)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council nurse rosters (part 3 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 45/53)
      - Seattle Area Hospital Council personnel policies and conditions, 1967 (Box-folder 46/1)
      - Seattle resignations, 1967 (Box-folder 46/2)
      - Seattle General Hospital, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 46/3)
      - Seattle-King County Department of Public Health, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 46/4)
      - Seattle-King County Department of Public Health supervisors, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 46/5)
      - Seattle Pediatric and Adolescent Center, 1966 (Box-folder 46/6)
      - Shelton General Hospital, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 46/7)
      - Skyline Hospital, White Salmon (part 1 of 2), 1957-1966 (Box-folder 46/8)
      - Skyline Hospital, White Salmon (part 2 of 2), 1957-1966 (Box-folder 46/9)
      - Snohomish County Public Health Department, 1953-1967 (Box-folder 46/10)
      - Southwest counties public health departments, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 46/11)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council (part 1 of 3), 1966-1969 (Box-folder 46/12)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council (part 2 of 3), 1966-1969 (Box-folder 46/13)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council (part 3 of 3), 1966-1969 (Box-folder 46/14)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council (part 1 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 46/15)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council (part 2 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 46/16)
      - Southwest Washington Hospital Council questionnaires, 1969 (Box-folder 46/17)
      - Southwest Washington hospitals, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 45/18)
      - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, Yakima, 1949-1966 (Box-folder 46/19)
      - St. Helens Hospital, Chehalis, 1951-1964 (Box-folder 46/20)
      - St. Ignatius Hospital, Colfax, 1953-1966 (Box-folder 46/21)
      - St. John's Hospital, Longview, 1957-1961 (Box-folder 46/22)
      - St. Joseph Hospital, Aberdeen, 1955-1967 (Box-folder 46/23)
      - St. Joseph Hospital, Vancouver, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 46/24)
      - St. Joseph's Hospital, Bellingham, 1952-1968 (Box-folder 46/25)
      - St. Joseph's Hospital, Tacoma, 1959-1967 (Box-folder 46/26)
      - St. Lukes General Hospital, Bellingham, 1952-1968 (Box-folder 46/27)
      - St. Lukes General Hospital, Bellingham supervisors, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 46/28)
      - St. Mary's Hospital, Walla Walla, 1954-1966 (Box-folder 46/29)
      - St. Peter's Hospital, Olympia, 1952-1961 (Box-folder 46/30)
      - Standring Memorial Hospital, Seattle, 1957-1962 (Box-folder 46/31)
      - Swedish Hospital, Seattle, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 46/32)
      - Tacoma General Hospital, 1953-1968 (Box-folder 46/33)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department, 1950-1958 (Box-folder 46/34)
      - Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 46/35)
      - United General Hospital, Sedro-Woolley, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 46/36)
      - Valley General Hospital, Monroe, 1955-1968 (Box-folder 46/37)
      - Valley General Hospital, Renton, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 46/38)
      - Visiting Nurse Association of Snohomish County, 1952-1969 (Box-folder 46/39)
      - Waldo General Hospital, Seattle, 1955-1961 (Box-folder 46/40)
      - Walla Walla General Hospital, 1966 (Box-folder 46/41)
      - West Seattle General Hospital, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 46/42)
      - Wesley Gardens, Des Moines, 1957-1966 (Box-folder 46/43)
      - Whatcom County Hospital, Bellingham, 1958-1965 (Box-folder 46/44)
      - Whitman County Health Department, 1966 (Box-folder 46/45)
      - Willapa County Hospital, South Bend, 1956-1964 (Box-folder 46/46)
      - Yakima County Health District case histories, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 46/47)
      - Yakima Valley Memorial Hospital (part 1 of 2), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 46/48)
      - Yakima Valley Memorial Hospital (part 2 of 2), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 46/49)
      - Private duty nurses, 1972 (Box-folder 57/12)
      - Private duty nurses, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 67/22)
      - Washington State. Department of Institutions, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 57/13)
      - Washington State. Department of Institutions, 1973 (Box-folder 57/14)
      - Washington State. Department of Institutions: local unit officers, 1973 (Box-folder 57/15)
      - Washington State. Department of Public Assistance, 1961-1971 (Box-folder 57/16)
      - Washington State. Department of Social and Health Services: nursing home consultants, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 57/17)
    - CORRESPONDENCE AND SUBJECT FILEs, 1946-1975; SUBSERIES II (Box-folder 6/21-7/38, 32/32-33/30, 47/1-47/26, 57/18-57/23, 67/23-67/25)
      - Seattle Area Nurse Representatives: minutes, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 6/21)
      - Economic Security Program: correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 6/22)
      - Economic Security Program: Margaret Ouchi correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - Costs of Economic Security Program, 1948-1962 (Box-folder 6/24)
      - Economic brief for the nursing profession for the State of Washington, 1948 (Box-folder 6/25)
      - Economic brief for the nursing profession for the State of Washington, 1949 (Box-folder 6/26)
      - Washington State Nurses' Association economic briefs, 1948-1957 (Box-folder 6/27)
      - Economic briefs for general duty nurses, 1949-1963 (Box-folder 6/28)
      - Economic briefs for public health nurses, 1951-1965 (Box-folder 6/29)
      - Research for public health briefs, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 6/30)
      - Economic Security Program material, 1956 (Box-folder 7/1)
      - Washington State Nurses' Association general duty advisory forum, 1960 (Box-folder 7/2)
      - Workshop of economic security, 1959 (Box-folder 7/3)
      - Conferences on Professional Practice and Employment Conditions, 1965 (Box-folder 7/4)
      - Economic relationships in nursing (proposed course), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Laws, rules, regulations and standards for nursing homes, 1960 (Box-folder 7/6)
      - Licensed practical nurses in public health agencies, undated (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Manual on economic security for all sections, 1957 (Box-folder 7/8)
      - Report on wages and working conditions for female workers in hospitals, State of Washington, 1961 (Box-folder 7/9)
      - American Nurses' Association reports, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 7/10)
      - Nursing home salaries, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 7/11)
      - Public health nurse salaries, 1964 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Beginning salary range for health departments in Washington State, 1965 (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Public health salaries out-of-state, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 7/14)
      - British Columbia, 1957-1965 (Box-folder 7/15)
      - Hawaii, 1962 (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Illinois, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Michigan, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 7/18)
      - New Mexico, 1964 (Box-folder 7/19)
      - New York strike, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Texas, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 7/21)
      - Wisconsin, 1965 (Box-folder 7/22)
      - American Nurses' Association Economic Security Program regional conferences, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - American Nurses' Association Statistical digest, 1953-1967 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - American Nurses' Association Trends in economics and industrial relations, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - American Nurses' Association Selected bibliography on economic security, 1963 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - American Nurses' Association Spot check of current hospital and nursing home employment conditions, 1962 (Box-folder 7/27)
      - American Nurses' Association news releases, 1960-1968 (Box-folder 7/28)
      - Agreement ballots and voting procedure, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 32/32)
      - California nurse salaries (part 1 of 2), 1954-1964 (Box-folder 32/33)
      - California nurse salaries (part 2 of 2), 1954-1964 (Box-folder 32/34)
      - California nurse salaries, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 32/35)
      - Collective bargaining representation, 1962 (Box-folder 32/36)
      - Chiefs, consultants, etc. salaries, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 32/37)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 32/38)
      - Child care deductions, 1963 (Box-folder 32/39)
      - Civil service salaries, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 32/40)
      - Economic security program sample questionnaires (part 1 of 2), 1954-1965 (Box-folder 32/41)
      - Economic security program sample questionnaires (part 2 of 2), 1954-1965 (Box-folder 32/42)
      - Economic Security News, 1969 (Box-folder 32/43)
      - Economic security reprints, 1946-1968 (Box-folder 32/44)
      - Employment standards: requests, 1969 (Box-folder 32/45)
      - Longevity pay plans, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 33/1)
      - Merchant Marine nurses, 1963 (Box-folder 33/2)
      - Mileage allowances for public employees, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Occupational health nurses NLRB certification, 1962 (Box-folder 33/4)
      - Psychiatric nurse salaries, 1964 (Box-folder 33/5)
      - State and Federal laws re collective bargaining, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 33/6)
      - Tacoma personnel rules, 1959 (Box-folder 33/7)
      - U.S. Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959 (Landrum-Griffin), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 33/8)
      - U.S. Manpower Development and Training Act, 1962 (Box-folder 33/9)
      - U.S. Minimum Wage and Hour Act, 1967 (Box-folder 33/10)
      - U.S. Public Health Service civilian nurses, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 33/11)
      - Veterans Administration - Executive Order 10988 (part 1 of 4), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 33/12)
      - Veterans Administration - Executive Order 10988 (part 2 of 4), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 33/13)
      - Veterans Administration - Executive Order 10988 (part 3 of 4), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 33/14)
      - Veterans Administration - Executive Order 10988 (part 4 of 4), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 33/15)
      - Veterans Administration nurses salaries, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 33/16)
      - Washington State Department of Health consultants salary justification, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 33/17)
      - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries, 1968 (Box-folder 33/18)
      - Washington State Equal Employment Opportunity Act, 1968 (Box-folder 33/19)
      - Washington State Initiatives 198 and 202, right to work laws, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 33/20)
      - Washington State law on collective bargaining for public employees, 1967 (Box-folder 33/21)
      - Washington State law on health districts, 1965 (Box-folder 33/22)
      - Washington State merit system rules / Initiatives 204 & 207, 1960 (Box-folder 33/23)
      - Washington State Minimum Wage and Hour Act, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 33/24)
      - Washington State minimum wage for women and minors, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 33/25)
      - Washington State salary ranges, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 33/26)
      - Washington State unemployment compensation, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 33/27)
      - Washington State Workmen's Industrial Insurance, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 33/28)
      - Washington State workmen's compensation, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 33/29)
      - Yakima County Public Health Department, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 33/30)
      - Correspondence with news media, 1966 (Box-folder 47/1)
      - Seattle Area Nurse Representatives, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 47/2)
      - Seattle Area Nurse Representatives - head nurses, 1965 (Box-folder 47/3)
      - American Nurses' Association economic security materials, 1958-1967 (Box-folder 47/4)
      - American Nurses' Association economic security materials, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 47/5)
      - American Nurses' Association reports on salaries and workloads of nursing teachers and administrators, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 47/6)
      - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers Section survey, 1962 (Box-folder 47/7)
      - Educators, Administrators, Consultants and Teachers Section economic security materials, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 47/8)
      - Employee handbooks, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 47/9)
      - Minnesota, 1952-1965 (Box-folder 47/10)
      - New York, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 47/11)
      - Personnel policies -- Washington State Hospital Association, 1967 (Box-folder 47/12)
      - Personnel policies -- hospitals in Washington State, 1960 (Box-folder 47/13)
      - Personnel policies -- King County hospitals, 1963 (Box-folder 47/14)
      - Personnel policies -- Seattle Public Schools, 1965 (Box-folder 47/15)
      - Personnel policies -- Federal government, 1956-1966 (Box-folder 47/16)
      - Personnel policies -- Washington State employees, 1965 (Box-folder 47/17)
      - Washington State economic security program, 1968 (Box-folder 47/18)
      - Economic Security Program reports, 1949-1956 (Box-folder 47/19)
      - Economic Security Program reports, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 47/20)
      - Economic Security Program reports, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 47/21)
      - Economic Security Program reports, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 47/22)
      - Reports to American Nurses' Association, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 47/23)
      - Reports to American Nurses' Association, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 47/24)
      - Reports to American Nurses' Association, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 47/25)
      - Reports to American Nurses' Association, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 47/26)
      - General correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 57/18)
      - Reports to American Nurses' Association, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 57/19)
      - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 57/20)
      - Bureau of National Affairs, 1970 (Box-folder 57/21)
      - Economic Security News, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 57/22)
      - Inquiries from registered nurses re: signed agreements, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 57/23)
      - Coalition of Health Care Employees, 1975 (Box-folder 67/23)
      - Washington State Department of Labor and Industries: employment standards, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 67/24)
      - Spokane Local Unit Coordinating Council, 1974 (Box-folder 67/25)
    - PUBLICITY RECORDS, 1955-1968; SUBSERIES III (Box-folder 7/29-7/43, 33/31-33/32)
      - Economic Security Program news releases, 1966 (Box-folder 7/29)
      - Economic Security Program news releases, 1967 (Box-folder 7/30)
      - News clippings, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 7/31)
      - King County Hospital (Harborview): clippings and news releases, 1966 (Box-folder 7/32)
      - Lillian Abrahamson Nursing Home, Everett: news clippings, 1968 (Box-folder 7/33)
      - Northgate Hospital: news clippings, 1967 (Box-folder 7/34)
      - Seattle negotiations: news clippings, 1967 (Box-folder 7/35)
      - Seattle-King County Department of Public Health: clippings and news releases, 1966 (Box-folder 7/36)
      - Spokane Hospitals: new clippings, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 7/37)
      - Yakima County Health District: clippings and news releases, 1966 (Box-folder 7/38)
      - Yakima Valley Memorial Hospital: news clippings, 1963 (Box-folder 7/39)